"老爸老妈的浪漫史"\n前情提要
Previously on How I Met Your Mother.
她太棒了, 她不可思议,幽默有趣而且...
She was completely amazing,she was amazing and funny and...
你对Ted有感觉
You have feelings for Ted?
也许
Maybe.
我刚收到来自一家烹饪学会的奖学金邀请
I've just been offered a fellowship\nat a culinary institute
在德国
in Germany.
想试试远距离恋爱吗?
Do you wanna try long distance?
要
Yes!
远距离恋爱遭透了?我今晚一定要和你谈谈
This long distance thing sucks, huh? And I really need to talk to you tonight.
她要甩了我
She's gonna dump me!
她不会和你分手的, Ted
She's not gonna break up with you, Ted.
喂?
Hello?
你想过来吗?
Do you wanna come over?
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-\n荣誉出品\n本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=cece&飞飞字幕组=-\n制作: 飞飞\n校对: 西西\n做最好的字幕，for the team,for dear baby
-=老爸老妈的浪漫史=-\n第一季 第18集
\nHow.I.Met.Your.Mother.\nSeason 01 Episode 18
孩子们, 你们的奶奶常说,凌晨两点以后不会有什么好事发生
Kids, your grandma always used to say to me,"Nothing good happens after 2:00 a.m,"
她是对的,凌晨两点就回家睡觉吧
and she was right,when 2:00 a.m. rolls around,just go home and go to sleep.
这就是一个好例子:
Case in point:
喂?
Hello?
嗨, Ted, 是Robin
Hi, Ted, it's Robin.
我知道已经很晚了, 但是
Listen, I know it's late,but
你想过来吗?
do you wanna come over?
让我们回溯一点
Let's back up a little
二十小时前
twenty hours ago
坐下
Sit.
好孩子, 好了, 记住
Good boys. Okay. Remember
不要碰酒柜
stay out of the liquor cabinet.
...电视播音员的生活是有益的
...So,the life of a television reporter\nis very rewarding,
我很希望你们能以此作为职业, 谢谢
and I strongly urge you to consider it as a career.Thank you.
说吧
Yeah.
你有未婚夫吗?
Do you have a fiance?
昨天Marshall来了,他们刚学会“未婚夫”这个词
Marshall was here yesterday.They just learned the word "fiance"
不, 我没有未婚夫
No, I don't have a fiance.
那你和谁住在一起?
Then who do you live with?
嗯，事实上, 我有五只狗
Well, actually, I've got five dogs.
你不会孤独吗?
Don't you get lonely?
不, 我有五只狗
No, I've got five dogs.
我奶奶有五只猫, 她觉得孤独
My Grandma has five cats and she gets lonely.
但那是猫, 我不是什么可悲的猫女士
Well, yeah, that's cats.I'm not some pathetic cat lady.
你奶奶也不是
Not that your grandmother is...
还有人有问题吗?
Does anyone else have a...
说吧
Yes.
你是同性恋吗?
Are you a lesbian?
不 你是吗?
No, are you?
一个人住并不代表就是同性恋...
Just because a woman lives alone doesn't mean she's a les...
好了
Okay.
让我们鼓掌感谢播音员Robin
Let's have a big hand for Robin the reporter!
好，我们的下一位客人是...
All right, our next guest is another friend...
Robin, 你报道过火车相撞吗?刚才我可见到了.
So, Robin, you ever report on train wrecks\ncause I just saw one. What up?
小小地击掌
Tiny five.
别看你现在笑的开心
Laugh now.
这些孩子是魔鬼,他们会把你活吞了
Those kids are monsters.They're gonna eat you alive.
他的工作是…
He has a job doing...
你是做什么的？
What do you do?
呵呵, 拜托
(chuckles):Please.
孩子们 我们来乐乐
Kids, let's rap.
你们对我怎么过活大概没什么兴趣
You guys don't give half a brown Crayola\nwhat I do for a living, do you?
对
No.
我知道你们想要什么.\n魔法!
No, no. I know what you want. \nMagic!
耶!
Yeah!
喂?
Hello?
为什么她还没打来?
Why hasn't she called yet?
好了, 你这样会把自己弄疯的
Okay, you're making yourself crazy.
现在是星期六的晚上, 出去玩玩吧
It's Saturday night.Go out and do something.
我干吗出去呢, 我有女朋友...眼下
No, what's the point of going out?\nI got a girlfriend. For now.
而且如果我出去谁看你们的新闻呢?
Besides, if I go out,who's gonna watch the news?
我提供了你们一半的收视率
I'm like half your viewership.
你说我们有两个观众高看我们了
I'm flattered you think we have two viewers.
暂停
And, we're clear.
Scherbatsky, 你有男朋友吗?
So, Scherbatsky. Got a boyfriend?
没有, 为什么今天老遇到这个问题
No, and why does this keep coming up today?
我以为和你打电话的是你男朋友
I just thought that guy you were on the phone with...
哦不, 那是Ted, 只是朋友
What? Oh, no. That was Ted.He's just a friend.
我们曾经有可能在一起
I mean, there was this moment where we almost dated,
但是我们想要的完全不同
but we want completely different things.
现在他有个女朋友在德国,他觉得她今晚会打电话来和他分手
Anyway, now he has his girlfriend in Germany and he thinks she's calling to dump him tonight,
但我想不会
but I don't think she is.
还有我们想要的完全不同
And, besides,we want completely different things.
我们应该上床
We should have sex.
什么?!
What?!
为什么不呢?
Why not?
我们都单身, 我们都很迷人
We're both available. We're both\nattractive.
而且我们都擅长此道, 至少我擅长
We're both good at it. At least, I'm good at it.
即使你不好, 也不用担心,我还是会很开心的
And even if you're not, don't worry.\nI'll have a good time either way.
我不敢想象你的发胶壳撞击床头板的画面
Well, moving past the horrifying image of your hair helmet clanging against the headboard
我不会和同事交往的
I don't get involved with people I work with.
交往? 谁说交往了?
Get involved? Who said get involved?
我只是说我们应该上床,没关系
I'm just saying we should have sex,it could be fun.
上床没关系
Having sex is fun.
我的号码, 有时间打给我
Home number. Call me anytime.
今晚有很多本地队伍的行动…
A lot of local teams in action tonight...
伙计们
Hey, guys.
想我吗?
Miss me?
我也想你们
I missed you, too.
嗨, Ted, 是Robin
Hi, Ted, it's Robin.
我知道已经很晚了, 但是
Listen, I know it's late,but
你想过来吗?
do you wanna come over?
Ted?\nTed?
哦, 是, 我在
Yeah. Hi, I'm here.
你想过来吗?
Do you wanna come over?
为什么? 怎么了?
Why? What's up?
我刚装好了果汁机,准备调点果汁
Well, I just finally set up my new juicer, and I was gonna make some juice.
然后我想, 谁喜欢果汁呢?
And I was like,You know who likes juice?
Ted!\nTed!
我爱果汁
I love juice.
太好了, 那你想过来做果汁吗?
Great, so you wanna come over and make juice?
凌晨两点以后, 睡觉吧
When it's after 2:00 a.m, just go to sleep
因为凌晨两点以后的决定都是错误的决定
Because the decisions you make after 2:00 a. m.are the wrong decisions
好, 我过来, 我们喝果汁
Okay, sure, I'll come over, we'll...juice.
对, 我们喝果汁
Yes, we'll juice.
好
Okay.
好, 再见
Okay, bye.
再见
Bye.
这没关系, 这完全没关系
This is fine. This is totally fine.
什么没关系?
What's fine?
哦, 我要去一个女孩家做果汁
Oh, I'm going over to this girl's house\nto make some juice.
呵呵, 好
Nice.
不, 不是你想的那样
No, it's not like that.
我们像朋友那样做果汁
We're juicing as friends.
我有女朋友, 我不会背叛她的
See, I have this girlfriend. I would never cheat on her.
她住在德国
She lives in Germany.
四个小时之前她就应该打电话跟我谈一个很严重的问题
See, she was supposed to call me four hours ago to have a serious talk.
但是到现在还没打, 我不知道...
I still haven't heard from her. I don't know...
对不起, 我的麻烦烦到你了
Sorry to bug you with my problems.
我猜出租车司机要变成酒吧招待了
Guess cab drivers are the new bartenders, huh?
说的一点也不错, 孩子
You ain't kidding, kid.
来点?
Want a nip?
就在这让我下吧
You could just let me out right up here.
去哪, 伙计
Where are you going to buddy?
公园街八号
Park Slope, Eighth and Eighth.
我和上个司机谈到这里为止
Okay, here's where I left off with the last guy.
我有女朋友,但我现在要去另一个女孩家
See, I have a girlfriend, but I'm going over\nto this other girl's house...
你想知道我会不会难过
And you're wondering if I'd be upset.
嗨,Ted 记得我吗? 你的女朋友
Hi,Ted.Remember me? Your girlfriend.
轻松点, Robin只是朋友
Okay, relax. Robin's just a friend.
对, 你要去做果汁
Right. You're gonna go make some juice.
对对, 果汁一点坏处也没有.\n事实上
Yes, yes. Juice is perfectly harmless.\nIn fact,
还很健康呢!
it's healthy.
是吗?那你为什么在想她是不是没穿衣服
Oh, yeah? Then why are you wondering\nwhat she looks like naked?
我没有在想...
I am not...
好吧, 如果我有想,也是你提醒我的
Okay, even if I am wondering that,it's only 'cause you put it in my head.
啊哈, 但我也在你的潜意识里,所以是你自己在想
But I am just a manifestation in your subconscious,,so actually, you put it in your own head.
TMD\nDamn it!
什么事都不会有的
Nothing's gonna happen.
对
Right.
好吧好吧, 你想听听别人的意见?行!
Okay, okay. You want a second opinion? Fine.
嗨, 她打来了吗？
Hey. Did she call?
没有, 我需要点提醒
No. I need a ruling.
也没什么大事情,我现在在去Robin家的路上
I'm... Yeah, this is stupid.It's not even a big deal,but I'm on my way over to Robin's,right now.
她有个新的果汁机什么的,我们要试试
She got a new juicer. Whatever.We're gonna test it out.
好, 我再打给你
Let me call you back.
亲爱的, 现在发生点情况
Honey, there's a situation developing.
你记得吗, 你告诉我一个大秘密
Do you remember the huge secret that you told me
你本不该说的, 是关于Robin的...
that you weren't supposed to, but you did? The thing about Robin?
是说Robin爱Ted的事?
You mean, how Robin's in love with Ted?
什么?
What?
她已经告诉我了, 继续
Yeah. She told me already. Go on.
我是她唯一没有告诉的人?
Wait. So I'm the only one that she didn't tell?
她告诉你没有告诉我?
She told you and not me?
我猜她只是认为我是比你更好的朋友
Well, I guess I'm just better friends\nwith her than you are.
但是我是Ted更好的朋友
Well, I'm better friends with Ted than you are.
你说谎
That is a lie.
没有
It is not a lie.
好 够了
Okay, that's it.
(BOTH SHOUTING)
快点接电话啊
Come on. Pick up.
Victoria你在哪? 接电话啊?
Damn it, Victoria. Where are you? Pick up,pick up
纸杯蛋糕?
Cupcake?
不, 谢谢\n你在哪? 为什么没有打电话?
No, thanks. \nWhere are you? Why haven't you called?
哦 我在外面玩
Oh,I'm out hooking up.
和三个男孩
With three other guys.
或者, 我是个专情的女友,现在正在打给你
Or maybe I'm a devoted girlfriend and I'm calling you right now.
对哦, 这我毫不怀疑
Yeah, why do I doubt that?
Ted, 我刚看了新闻:一辆满载硫酸的卡车
Hello?Ted. I just saw the news,and a truck carrying sulfuric acid
在Robin家门前倾覆
overturned right in front of Robin's house.
人行道被融出一个大洞
And it's melting through the sidewalk,
从洞里可以直接看到地狱
You can see straight down into Hell.
太可怕了
It's bad.
你应该回家, 哥们儿
You should go home, dude.
Marshall没事的, 什么都不会发生
Marshall, it's fine.Nothing's gonna happen.
Ted, 你妈总是怎么说?
Ted, what does your mom always say?
凌晨两点之后不会有好事情发生
Nothing good ever... Nothing good ever happens after 2:00 a.m.
回家! 现在喝果汁太晚了
Go home! It's too late for juice.
Robin和我只是朋友,她对我没有那方面的意思
Dude, Robin and I are just friends.\nShe doesn't even like me that way.
不, 她有,她告诉我她喜欢你
Yes, she does! She likes you. She told me.
什么?
What?
这是秘密,所以不要告诉她我告诉你的
It's a big secret. So don't tell her I told you
但现在她很脆弱,而你也有女朋友
but she's very vulnerable right now,and you have a girlfriend.
回家 Ted
Go home, Ted.
她喜欢我?
She likes me?
是的!\n所以你现在过去绝对是个坏主意
Yes!\nSo you see why it would be a very bad idea for you to go up there
回家 Ted
Go home, Ted
她喜欢我?
She likes me?
回家 Ted
Go home, Ted.
好, 家里见
You're right, I'll...I'll see you at home.
好了, 他回家了
Good. He's going home.
他不会回家的
He is so not going home.
真不相信你告诉他了
I cannot believe you just told him that.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
Lily 这就是你的话的意思：
Lily, here's what you just said,
Ted, 不管你去哪, 别去那
Ted, whatever you do,don't go up there.
因为那里有个漂亮女孩想和你上床
There's a beautiful girl who wants to have sex with you.
而且她还会为你准备美味的果汁
And then she's gonna make you some delicious juice!
不, 他不会去的, 他有理性
No. He's not going up there.\nHe has more sense than that.
我确实有理性
I did have more sense than that
不用找了.谢谢
Keep the change. Thanks.
但是凌晨两点以后 我的理性都睡着了\nBut after 2：a.m.my good sense was sound asleep
你要这么做? 你要进去?
So, you're doing this?\nYou're going up there?
你要拦我?
You want to get out of the way?
我没有拦你
I'm not in the way.
你知道, 如果你打给我,我一定...
You know, if you had just called me, I...
-嗨！\n-嘿.
-Hi!\n-Hey.
我带了蔬菜来,有胡萝卜,豆子
I got some vegetables. I got carrots.\nI got beets.
我们就喝酒吧
Or we could just drink wine.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
这是我说的最蠢的话
Wow, that's the stupidest thing I ever said.
-用大杯\n-好的
-Make it a big glass. \n-Sure.
过的怎么样?
So, how's it hanging?
你有没有这样过,也没什么发生
Haven't you ever had one of those days where nothing at all that monumental happens,
但是你忽然不知道你自己是谁,你在过什么样的生活?
but, by the end of it, you have no idea who you are anymore,what the hell you're doing with your life?
你有这样吗?
Do you ever have one of those days?
每周一次
About once a week.
我不知道, 只是难熬的一天
I don't know. It was just a rough day,
在这一天结束的时候，我唯一想见的就是你
and the only person I wanted to see\nat the end of it was you.
你女朋友的电话怎么说了?
So, how was the big phone call with your girlfriend?
时针指向两点, 睡觉吧\nWhen the clock strikes two，just go to sleep
我们分手了
We broke up.
什么?
What?
对, 她终于打来了, 我们谈了一会
Yeah. Yeah. She finally called.
说了说远距离恋爱有多难,
We talked for a while.How hard long distance is,
然后，她甩了我
and then she dumped me.
Ted我很遗憾，这太遭了, 我感觉遭透了
Ted, I'm so sorry. That's just terrible. I feel awful.
你在笑
You're smiling.
是吗?
Am I?
我没有
No, I'm not.
我是播新闻的, 这是职业笑容
Well, I'm a news anchor. Smiling is a part of the job.
今天的雪崩造成数千人丧生
Thousands died in a tragic avalanche today.
看到了?
See?
你也在笑
You're smiling, too.
对, 我不知道这是怎么回事
Yeah. I have no idea what that's all about.
这个韩国猫王有多酷?
How much does Korean Elvis rock?
我自己回答: 无限
I'll answer that. Infinity.
他无限的酷
He rocks infinity.
好了, 该睡觉了
Okay, it's time for bed.
什么? 不! 才2:30
What? No. It's 2:30.
凌晨两点之后不会有好事情发生
And nothing good ever happens after 2:00 a.m.
我发现, 在我的人生旅程
You know, I have found in my travels
所有好的事情都发生在凌晨两点之后
that all the best things in life happen after 2:00 a.m.
回头想想, 我生命中最美妙的故事\nWhen I look back，at the best stories of my life,
"自由钟事件"
the Liberty Bell incident,
"俄国大使馆事件"
the little scrape I got in at the Russian embassy
"差点就成了的四人行"
the almost four-way.
-你从来没四人行，\n-我说了差点...\n-好，好
-You never had a four-way.\n-I said "almost"!\n-Well, all right.
所有的事都是凌晨两点后发生的
All those things happened after 2:00 a.m.
因为凌晨两点以后一切才会变的
Because after 2:00 a.m. is when things get,
观众们和我一起说: 传奇性的!
audience, say it with me, legendary!
我要走了
We going home.
你说什么? 理论很有意思, Barney，但是我们要证明.
What's that? "Interesting theory, Barney, "but I'll need some proof." Okay.
韩国猫王, 想和我和我的朋友喝一杯吗?
Korean Elvis. How would you like\nto have a drink with me and my friends?
摇滚吧
Rock 'n' roll.
开始了
And it begins.
嘿, 我买了个新手机,和你的一样,看.
So,hey.I got a new phone. Same as yours. Look.
哦 是啊, 你喜欢吗?
Oh, yeah, do you like it?
对 对
Yeah.Yeah.
这个手指略有微辞
This is some solid small talk.
我还有个手机, 也不错
I had that other phone, and it was good,
但是一直以来, 部分的我
but I think, the whole time,a little part of me
想换这只手机代替那只
wanted this phone instead.
因为这只
This phone
有对的感觉
feels right.
哇 奇怪
Oh, wow. Weird.
对
Yeah,
我想私下接
I should probably take this.
我在这等你
I'll be here.
喂?
Hello?
Ted, 这里是NKE电台
Ted. This is your main man N.K.E.
我要你尽快服用安眠药, 可以吗?
I want you to shake your tail feather\ndown here ASAP. You dig?
对不起
Okay. Sorry about that.
刚才那是韩国猫王?
Who... Was that Korean Elvis?
我以后再解释, 我们正去MacLaren酒吧.
I'll explain later.Hey, we're heading down to MacLaren's.
事实上
Actually
我在Robin家,对,而且,
I'm at Robin's.Yeah, and,um...
我做了点坏事,我刚骗她说我和Victoria分手了
I might have done something bad.I just lied and told her I broke up with Victoria.
Ted我不想在韩国猫王面前说脏话,但是你他-Beep-的要做什么!
Ted, I don't want to swear in front of Korean Elvis,but what the bleep are you doing, dude?
我还能怎么样?是Robin啊! Victoria很好
What do you expect from me? It's Robin! Victoria's great,
但这是Robin啊!
but it's Robin!
我已经决定, 我要和Victoria分手
I've made up my mind,I'm gonna end it with Victoria.
要分手?
Gonna?
对, 明天第一件事
Yes. First thing tomorrow.
但是现在, 凌晨两点四十五
Okay, but as of right now, at 2:45 a.m.
你还是有女朋友的
You still have a girlfriend.
Ted我爱你, 我爱Robin
Ted, I love you. I love Robin.
但是如果你现在这么做
But if you do this right now,
你们俩的未来都将是建立在一个谎言的基础上
your entire future with her will be built on a crime!
回家吧, Ted, 不要做错事
Just go home, Ted,Don't do this the wrong way!
我讨厌你总是对的
I hate how you're always right.
这是我最好的也是最烦人的一次特征.
It's my best and most annoying trait.
好吧, 我回家, 一会见
Okay. I'm coming home. I'll see you soon.
- 嘿.\n- 嘿.
- Hey.\n- Hey.
我应该走了, 很晚了
I should probably get going.It's pretty late.
- 对不起, 我\n- 不, 我明白, 没关系
- I'm sorry. I...\n- Oh, no. I understand. It's fine. Yeah.
明天我能打电话给你吗?
Can I call you tomorrow?
当然 当然 明天打给我
Totally.Totally. Call me tomorrow.
好
Okay.
- 晚安Robin\n- 晚安Ted
- Good night, Robin.\n- Good night, Ted.
噢,老天, 我们在亲热?
Oh, my God! We're making out.
是吗，是吗，是吗!这太疯狂了.
Right!This is crazy.Right! Right!
我们应该进房间吗?
Should we go to my room?
那有五只狗, 但是
I mean, there's five dogs in there, but...
好
Yeah.
-好吗?\n-好.
-Yeah?\n-Yeah.
我...我得去下洗手间,很快
I just, I have to run to the bathroom.\nReal quick.
好.
Okay.
别再这样了
Stop doing that!
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我要打电话给你, 我们要分手
I'm calling you. We're breaking up.
我现在就要这么做
I'm doing this right now.
走出这个洗手间的时候就是单身了
I'm coming out of this bathroom a single man.
好, 但是Ted,你认为我们的谈话要花多长时间?
Okay. Say, Ted, how long do you think\nthat conversation's gonna be?
和一般尿尿的时间一样?
Length of an average pee?
不, 我们的电话至少要20分钟
No. We're gonna be on the phone for at least 20 minutes.
Robin就在外面.她会认为你在这里打...
Robin's out there.She's gonna think\nyou're in here taking a massive...
你要我怎么做? 人们会分手
What do you want from me?People break up.
这会发生
It happens.
但不是这样分手
Not like this.
不是在你马上要和她做爱的女孩的洗手间
Not from the bathroom of the girl that you're about to sleep with.
这是不太理想
It's not ideal.
再说酒吧里
Meanwhile, back at the bar
Barney还想证明凌晨两点后可能发生好事
Barney was still trying to prove that\ngood things can happen after 2:00 a.m.
拜托Lily!有多少女人能享受韩国猫王为她单独唱小曲
Come on, Lily! How many women can say they've been personally serenaded by Korean Elvis?
我想他刚刚向我吐口水了
I think he just spat on me.
Barney你尝试过了,这很棒, 我们要走了
Barney,you tried.I think that's great.\nBut we're going.
哦 不 不 拜托
No. No, come on!
要!
Yes!
伙计我们还没看到神奇的事,我们才看到“神”, 还有“奇”呢
Dude.We haven't hit legendary yet."We're only at the "le." We still got the "gen," the "da," the "ry.
如果我们已经看到“神”, 不如回家吧\n（legendry和let's go home都以le开头）
Okay, if we're at the "le," then I say we follow it up with a "t's go home."
哇,你受到打击了
Oh, wow! You just got burned.Phonics style!
宝贝宝贝 不要走,再跳支舞吧
No, no, no, no. Baby, baby, baby, don't go. Just one dance, huh?
好了, 我是认真的
Okay, seriously.
我知道你想要什么
Hey, I know what you like.
于是, Barney是对的
And so, Barney was right
这一夜是传奇性的
The night was legendary
这后来被大家称为Lily踢韩国猫王蛋蛋的一夜
It would come to be known as the time Lily kicked Korean Elvis in the nards
你们记得Lily踢韩国猫王蛋蛋的那天?
Hey, you guys remember that time that Lily kicked Korean Elvis in the nards?
你是对的,我欠你一个真正的分手电话
You're right. You're right. I owe you a real breakup call.
我明早打给你
I'll call you tomorrow.
好, 那你回家吗?
Good. So, you're gonna go home?
为什么我一定要回家?
Why should I have to go home?
有可能Robin就是我以后要娶的女人
You know, there's every chance Robin's the woman I'm gonna marry.
Ted\nTed.
这有可能!
It could happen!
五十年之后这又会有什么关系,只是跳过一夜
And so, really, what's it gonna matter\nin 50 years if I jump the gun by one night?
我知道这不符合道德, 但...
Look,I know this is a moral gray area, but...
是Robin啊
it's Robin.
我精疲力竭了,我精疲力竭是因为要装作不爱她
And I'm exhausted. I am. I'm exhausted from pretending I'm not in love with her.
我想这是个充分的理由
I think that makes this okay.
得了, 你只是想和她上床
Oh, please. You just want to get laid!
是的, 我是, 你说对了
Yes, I do. You got me.
这就是现在我想要的, 那又如何?
That is exactly what I want right now.\nAnd so what?
我想要, 她也想要, 这事发生了
I want this. She wants this.
如果你不乐意, 不要在德国
It's happening. And if you have a problem\nwith it, don't be in Germany!
假装和你谈话很愉快
It's been nice pretending to talk to you.
谢谢你没有打电话给我, 晚安
Thanks for not calling me and good night.
那不是你的电话
That's not your phone.
这不是我的电话
This isn't my phone.
好的, 再见
Okay. Bye.
我以为是我的, 所以接了
I thought it was mine, so I answered it.
是谁?
Was it...
是你女朋友
It was your girlfriend.
你可能想打回去给她
You might want to call her back.
我在出租车上打给了Victoria,我们分手了
I called Victoria from the cab,and we broke up.
对
Yes, I'm...
现在你们知道了, 孩子们
And there you have it, kids
我做过的最愚蠢的事情
The stupidest thing I've ever done
在一夜我伤害了两个我最在乎的人
In one night, I managed to hurt two people I cared about
如果我听妈妈的话, 这都不会发生
And none of it would've happened if I had just listened to my mom
所以我想,我们要从中吸取的教训是
So, I guess if there's a lesson to be learned here, it's this
凌晨两点以后
when it's after 2:00 a.m.
睡觉吧
just go to sleep